<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<books>
  <book ID="Quotes" Title="Quotes">
    <page>
"Strap this around your temples. Stop yammering, you will be fine.
What could possibly go wrong?"
[[-Argyve, Tinker]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Breathe deep the breath of gods, and die."
[[-Ekuemekiyyen inscription]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Black devils swing from starry masts,
beneath the Yawning Moon."
[[-Fuming God Sea shanty]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Today we shove off our frozen haunts, across bleak Arthax, and spy
for those inverted hills of chrome."
[[-Consul Ijulii's farewell]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Who inhabits the colossal desert freehold of Nanru? The Gathered Men.
The fiefdoms of Odrum? The Kneeling Men.
The jungles of Yyp? The Breathless Men.
And the rust-caves of Qud? The Screaming Men."
[[-Dromad travelogue]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Live and drink, friend. Now give me your water."
[[-Courteous bandit]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Moon and Sun; wisdom and will."
[[-Watervine farmer's prayer]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Praises due to the most high, thy Argent Father, me."
[[-Shekhinah]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Look on my riches, ye Wealthy, and despair! (but do not touch)"
[[-Hegelrut]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Yes, I know the secrets of the circuitry mind. It's a flaming
wonder, telepath."
[[-Seeker of the Sightless Way]]
    </page>
    <page>
"It burns!"
[[-Argyve's apprentice]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Rule with a tungsten carbide fist."
[[-King K4K5]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Alas, I'd make a slumberling divine,
for in the dreaming dale art thou yet mine."
[[-Willow Shakesprig]]
    </page>
    <page>
"There it is in all of us -- shades of our elder selves. Within each
man, a goat. Within each goat, a man!"
[[-Wild-eyed watervine merchant]]
    </page>
    <page>
"What is the nature of this thing we bludgeon? Or of the act itself?"
[[-Mayor Nuntu]]
    </page>
    <page>
"To ply those silver hollows -- a spry adventurer's dream!"
[[-Elder Irudad]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Don't heed the tale of every thirsty fool."
[[-Ol' Uri]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Grrrraaaah."
[[-Warden Indrix]]
    </page>
    <page>
"May you bathe in blood. Not your own blood, sir. The blood of the
recast. I mean, the reclaimed. May you bathe in the blood of the
reclaimed."
[[-Putus squire]]
    </page>
    <page>
"May you bathe in the blood of the reclaimed."
[[-Putus templar]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Do those legs absorb water? Do they even synthesize cytokinins? I
didn't think so."
[[-Consortium Socialite]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Upon hearing the news of the king's death, Uutut's political
adversaries cheered Wysterwort as a hero. They were soon disabused."
[[-The Baccata Yewtarch]]
    </page>
    <page>
"I have gazed into the hundred nine eyes of Shug'ruith the Burrower."
[[-Barathrum the Old]]
    </page>
    <page>
"May the ground shake but the Six Day Stilt never tumble!"
[[-Song of Hebronze]]
    </page>
    <page>
"O, wise men! Keep thyselves assured wise,
and where a maid approacheth, shut thine eyes."
[[-Willow Shakesprig]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Nay, you should desire none of these things, for we are ravenous
fiends and oft succumb to fits of maddened fury."
[[-The Madpole]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Erecting a lodge is no paltry charge. Near all of my day is spent
chipping and stacking wood, and though you marvel at the lodge
itself, you may scowl at the labor that brings it forth."
[[-The Musker]]
    </page>
    <page>
"In all these things you may with us partake, but take heed, for ours
are idle lives, and you may soon grow weary of them."
[[-The Gnu]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Klanq puff at you."
[[-Pax Klanq]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Feast upon the goat hearts!"
[[-Mamon Souldrinker]]
    </page>
    <page>
"Now Elohart and Belahind lie in a field of lah
because their fields got hungry and devoured the faundren raw."
[[-Bey Lah nursery rhyme]]
    </page>
    <page>
"You determine your worthiness! You steer it and shape it with
your words and deeds! Now will you wallow in your abject limitations,
or will you face me with everything you have?"
[[-Carbide Chef Agate Severance Star]]
    </page>
    <page>
"It is my dearest hope that one day I shall be known not as Angohind,
village bookworm... but Angohind, Master Detective."
[[-Angohind, village bookworm]]
    </page>
  </book>
</books>
